Thank you for watching!
Thanks again for all your hard work!
Hello! This time I'm joined by Gashion Tamura from Angulum and Yumi Kasai from Tsubaki Factory.
This time, I'm going to introduce you to the two of them, so please bear with me until the end.
We're in the same grade, right?
Yes, that's right.
And we're from the same city in the next prefecture, so I have a sense of kinship with you.
I haven't talked to Yumi that much, but...
But...
When I go to Yamanashi Prefecture, I talk to Yumi.
I wondered if Yumi would be there since we are from the same city in the next prefecture.
I wonder if you are there.
Thank you very much for your kindness.
I also feel very close to you because we are from neighboring prefectures.
I would like to play together with you.
I'm very happy to be able to perform at Halo! I am very happy to be able to perform with you in this way.
Thank you very much.
As for our recent activities, we have started our autumn tour.
Angelem 10th anniversary tour 2024 autumn Roots is going on!
Tsubaki Factory Live Tour 2024 Autumn, which means "the heartbeat." Tsubaki Factory is holding an autumn live house tour.
This autumn tour is to commemorate the 10th anniversary of Angelem.
We hope you'll enjoy the songs filled with Angelem's charms.
What is the most memorable episode in your recent life?
As a matter of fact, one of the most memorable episodes was
On the day of Ms. Hashizako's birthday
on the day of Mr. Hashizako's birthday.
So the show was in Mr. Hashizako's hometown
so it was also
So it was a special day that it was both his birthday and a performance in his hometown.
So we decided to celebrate Mr. Hashizako's birthday with all the fans and all the members including the staff.
It was wonderful!
I was really impressed when he wished Mr. Hashizako a happy birthday during the MC.
Wow, what a great episode!
Thank you very much.
Yes, we, Tsubaki Factory, including myself, are in the same class.
It's the first time for the younger members to go on a live house tour, so we are very close to the audience, and it's a lot of fun to deliver our thoughts and feelings to them,
On the other hand, the reactions we get from the audience are amazing and immediate, which makes me very happy,
Tsubaki Factory has a lot of songs in spring, summer, fall, and winter.
Tsubaki Factory has a lot of songs in spring, summer, fall, and winter, so I think we'll be able to present our autumn and winter songs to you all.
Wow!
What was your most memorable memory recently?
Touring around the local area.
I've been to many prefectures in Japan.
I've been to many prefectures, and I've been catered to the local delicacies of each area, and I've been so impressed with the local cuisine.
It makes me feel like I'm in love with the place.
It's nice, isn't it?
When you get to eat the food that you want to eat because you've been there, it's like a sign that you've been there.
It's like a proof that I've been there.
Please watch the video below.
me
w o o
me w o car
me
Why
I don't have a choice.
It's true, it's true, it's true, it's true
If we succeed, I'll be happy.
It's true, it's true, it's true, it's true.
True True True
And now I'm living here.
I don't know how long I've been here.
It's warm, like a sleepy village.
I really want to protect someone
Rar.
I can't let them take my heart, I can't let them break it.
I have to trust myself
My No Good Son
I was born into this world without a purpose
And now that I'm older
Something like a sense of mission
It is true that I was born
Not knowing what to experience
I feel the fruit between the kids
Fruit between kids I feel fruit like a village
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
If you really want to protect someone, you don't like the eye of light
You say it's common sense, but I guess it depends on your point of view.
I've had it, I've had it, I've had it, I've had it, I've had it.
I just have to trust myself.
Why not?
Let's take it easy today.
Shion Tamenaga of Anjirum
and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory bring you Halo! stay!
From here, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
so let's answer in a quick tempo without thinking too much.
I'll do my best.
Halo! Project Stream.
I went to Beijing to support Sakura Japan.
Paris bullet trip to support Sakura Japan in Beijing is now on view!
We look forward to seeing you soon!
What was your most memorable experience in Paris?
Seeing the Arc de Triomphe and the Eiffel Tower.
After hockey and Yamanashi, what would you say is synonymous with Yuko Kasai?
History
Oh!
Tsubaki Factory is in the middle of a tour of nearly 40 shows in all.
What do you keep in mind for conditioning?
I lick my favorite throat lozenges.
What do you keep in mind when you sing?
I sing with the feeling of delivering the music to the audience. Four months have passed since the current 11-member lineup was formed.
What has changed in you, and how did you remember your first love?
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
I mean, I'm a history buff...
I like trivia about history, and I also like visiting temples and shrines, and temples and shrines are sometimes related to history.
I also like to visit temples and shrines myself, and since temples and shrines are related to history, I went to Kyoto the other day to visit temples and shrines by myself.
I like visiting temples and shrines by myself, and the temple I visited in Kyoto was called Kuramadera, which was built by Minamoto Yoshitsune in the Kamakura period (1185-1333).
The temple in Kyoto is called Kuramadera, where Minamoto no Yoshitsune lived as a child.
I also climbed a mountain that is said to be haunted by tengu (long-nosed goblins), and I visited a place where such a historical person lived.
I like places where historical figures have lived.
I also like the Kamakura Shogunate, so I go to Kamakura and so on.
I like a wide range of eras.
Another thing that caught my attention is what you keep in mind when you sing.
Yes, I do.
Yes, yes.
I've been on a live house tour recently for the fall tour, and I'm very close to the audience, so I think it's important to deliver my feelings.
I'm very conscious of delivering the message to the audience because I'm close to them.
In order to convey our feelings, we are very conscious of singing with our whole body, including our face, voice, and tone of voice.
I really like your singing voice.
I'm so glad to know that you were conscious of this, because I really like your voice and it reaches me.
Thank you very much for your kind attention.
me
Good morning.
Today is the day to work hard.
Today, I'll probably put on the doubling of the unlucky part, etc., and then I wonder what I'll do after that. I'm not sure if I'm going to go through the block or what, but I feel like I can do something.
I can see the completion of the project.
Music
I've missed two days of work, and now I'm paying for it.
I saw the video and thought, "This is it, I'm going to go through between who and who.
But when I actually stand up, it's totally different, and I think it's very difficult.
Mandalia in my heart I'm not afraid to doubt
Life is funny, everyone talk about it
With the foundation, we exchange musical letters and
The tension of the pull and the exchange, the best part of music is
Next, I would like to ask Mr. Tamura some questions
I'll do my best.
Next weekend marks the 4th anniversary since I joined Angulum
Looking back over the past four years, what is the first thing that comes to mind?
Standing in Yokohama Arena.
The new single "Yuyukankan Ganavia Line".
How do you quickly forget about the things you don't care about?
Reading shoujo manga (girls' manga).
What are you personally interested in now?
Running marathons
What do you keep in mind when you dance?
Feelings
About a month until Ms. Kawamura's graduation
What is the Kawamura-ism that you want to inherit?
Always give my all
It was wonderful!
I'd like to delve into the part that caught my attention.
How to forget about unimportant things...
Shoujo manga (girls' manga)
I like them a lot, yes, I really like them.
I like them a lot, and I've tried many different kinds of stories, but...
I'm sure I'll think about it a lot... and maybe I should buy them and go see a different story... and maybe I'll forget about them.
I'll go to bed... like us I like shoujo manga too... please recommend them to me.
I'd like to know what you're thinking about when you dance.
I'm not sure how I feel when I'm dancing, but sometimes I really feel the emotion of the song.
Sometimes the feelings of the song are expressed directly in the song, and other times the song has a live feel, so you can share the fun with the audience and make eye contact with them.
I share with the audience and make eye contact with them, and that's how the dance gets bigger and bigger on its own.
I've been told that I'm passionate, that I'm giving it my all.
I've always loved your dance and thought it was so cool, so I'll be referring to it.
I'm going to use it as a reference. Stay tuned for more after this!
Thank you for watching!
October 10th is
Cheers Youth Day
Cheers!
Cheers.
Next, I'd like to try a project like this.
Let's call it
Shuffle Live Show
What songs will be sung and by how many people?
Who will sing what songs and who will sing them
and who will sing what songs and who will sing them.
This is a very exciting project!
It's a shuffle unit!
I'm so excited!
Oh, no!
What?
I'm sorry, I love the Aigirls.
Four?
I wonder who they are.
And this is where the members are decided.
I see.
I'm so excited.
This is important.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
My eyes are dirty.
Great luck with synchronization.
Next, Sakura Ishiyama.
Oh!
Welcome, welcome
Last is
Inomirei.
Inomirei
The best!
Please, have a strategy meeting.
Mr. Rey, you're my senior.
I'll give it to you because you're my senior.
Because I'm your senior, does that mean I get to decide?
Okay, let's start with the "I love you" screen.
Let's get started.
Sorry about this song.
It's splitting your eyes.
In the middle of the dance
Summer and the so-called days
My heart is getting tired of gathering
I'm getting hungry
I'm always warming up before
I know what tomorrow will bring
It's been a long time since I've seen you.
Three Friends.
Pull now.
Let's go.
Eva! Eva!
It's Kresser.
What are you looking at?
There's garbage on the floor, isn't there?
I know it's on the floor.
Okay, here we go.
Inoue.
Amazing.
Miracle!
I'm coming.
It's me.
Ichiko.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Nenri-ne start
on the approaching Iwatobaru mountain
I don't know what will happen
A crucial moment
I always laugh too
I'm not well
Are you
Are you ready?
What times we live in
The age of rules.
Don't panic
Follow the path
When the real thing comes
There's always one up ahead
That's enough.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
We're going to start our 17-lap live corner.
I hope you're all enjoying yourselves.
First up is this song.
Say I love you.
I gotta say it out loud and clear.
I still love you
Yeah
Dream, dream, dream
I still love you
With all my heart on my toes
I'll touch you with my skirt
But I don't care about that
I'm a little stronger than I was back then
I'm a little stronger now
The next era's beginning
Someday our future
Will be destroyed
Now
Our future
Crush
Now
Our future
Crush
crush
JuiceJuice FC Event 2024 October 10 is the end of JuiceJuice day.
Thank you very much.
This JuiceJuice Day event started as a play on words,
Thank you very much for holding this event again this year.
This time, we wanted to make it a unique FC event,
How did you enjoy it?
How was it? It was really warm.
I felt really safe because of the atmosphere created by the fans.
It was fun.
It was very unusual to start the JuiceJuice song with "Magic of Love," which was performed by all the members,
Mirai-san Run Out" and other songs that we hadn't been able to perform in a while,
The corners were a lot of fun.
It was fun.
I was impressed again by how well we responded to the audience and how well the fans responded to us.
It was really fun. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
That's all for Kyushu City.
Bye bye.
This is Halo! Ste.
From here, we will be back with the Halo! Pro Next Week.
This time, we'll introduce the schedule of Halo! Project's schedule from October 24th to October 30th.
Here it is.
Oh, I see, they are doing a lot of fall tours.
All the groups are doing a lot of tours.
Tsawaki Factory is one of them.
For the first time in Nagasaki and Saga.
That's great.
Yes, that's great.
Anjury will also have a talk session.
The Villons will have a traveling classical piano and violin concert of masterpieces.
So there is such a thing.
Yes, so I was wondering if you would be interested in any of these,
I want to talk about an event that I'm going to attend,
There will be an online talk session,
I'm going to be there on October 30,
I will be participating in this with.live online talk session on October 30, and every time I do it, it's to celebrate the release of a single,
It's a very close event,
I think it's an event where we are very close to each other,
I prepare a lot of goods of my favorite members for the background,
Some fans prepare a lot of backgrounds with goods of their favorite members,
There are also fans who prepare a lot of backgrounds with goods of their favorite members, and there are those who do it on their way home after work,
I was surprised to hear that they are really doing this kind of thing now,
I think,
The distance between us may be long, but I feel that our hearts are very close, which is why I really like this event.
Yes, I was interested in the BEYONDZ Honoka Kobayashi traveling classical piano and violin concert of masterpieces,
This is a concert in which Ms. Kobayashi will participate alone,
I'm really interested in this concert, and Ms. Kobayashi's piano is really wonderful, so I'd like to go see it.
I'm really interested in this concert, and I'd like to go see it because Ms. Kobayashi's piano is so wonderful.
I'd like to go see the concert because it's a different kind of concert than a group concert.
When we participate in individual events, we are not a part of the group, so we are a little nervous, but at the same time we want to take this chance.
I'm a little nervous, but at the same time, I feel that this is a good chance for us to get to know the name of the group more and more.
We are working hard to make our group's name known more and more.
So we are working hard to make our group's name known more and more, so that we can be more active.
We would like to have more people know about us when we participate in Sakura Japan's events in Beijing and so on.
So we are very happy to have the opportunity to be known as a group.
You never know what will lead people to know the name of our group.
We will continue to do our best!
If you can make it to one of our events, please come and spend some time with us and the Hello Project!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Have you been working too hard lately? Don't push yourself too hard.
This is Halostepp featuring Shion Tanaka of Angelem
and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
It's time to say goodbye.
I've been wanting to film Haloste with you for a long time.
I've been wanting to shoot Haloste with Yumi for a long time.
I'm so happy!
That's why I'm so happy that it came true.
I've been wanting to talk with you more and more, so I'm sure we'll have something in common.
I'd like to have dinner with you in the future.
Here is an announcement!
Anjelm's 10th anniversary tour 2024 autumn roots is coming up next weekend in Kanagawa!
We are in the middle of our tour right now, and we are really celebrating our 10th anniversary.
The final show will be held on Thursday, November 28th at Nippon Budokan.
The final event of this tour will be held at Nippon Budokan on Thursday, November 28th.
This final show of the tour will be the graduation show of Ms. Kawamura, so we will miss her very much, but we are looking forward to seeing you all there.
As the title says, it's the final show of the tour.
As the title says, we would like to bring you a sparkling and glittering Angiarium.
Please come and join us.
Tsubaki Factory Live Tour 2024 Autumn Heartbeat
This weekend at Nagasaki Saga Park
This autumn tour will feature many songs that will make you feel the winter and autumn of Tsubaki Factory.
Please come and see us.
Also, our new singles, "Hatsukoi Hanabie" and "Yuyuukankan Kanakananaibi Light" will be released on November 13.
These two songs are completely different from each other.
The song is about a fleeting and sad first love.
And Yuyukankanganobihorai is a cheerful and energetic cheer-up song,
Please listen to both songs and get them. Please listen to both songs and get them.
Please listen to both songs and get them. Project members will appear more and more in the "Halo! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
Project members. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us high ratings, comments, and subscribe to our channel.
The other two were Shio Tanaka of Angulum and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
Goodbye!